we are Chechens to shed blood for Russia and
мы чеченцы кровь проливать за России а
we wear military uniforms and you wear
мы в военный форма ходить а ты на рыбу
military uniforms to go fishing. Well, where is the military,
ходить в военный формах Ну а где военна
where is this, no buttonholes, nothing, well,
где же это ни петлиц ничего нету Ну это
no insignia, not exactly, well,
Никаких знаков отличия ни точно Ну
show me nothing, no, no, this, this,
покажи ничего нет не не не это это это
even Velcro  no You
даже липучки нету Ты
see salam
видишь салам
alaikum alaikum salam Where are you from brother
алейкум алейкум салам Вы откуда брат
and where are you from Gurme Chechen Republic
а ты откуда Гурме Чеченская республика
Iria alaikum ahma power Where are you from Ah
ирия алейкум ахма сила Ты откуда Ах
Mala
мала
Ural you are
Урал ты
a Chechen who are you an Uzbek
чеченец кто ты узбек
Uzbek understood how the
узбек понял как как там
Russians don’t treat our
русские не относятся плохо к нашему
Muslim brother badly
брату мусульманину
with a bang not there Ramzan Akhmatovich built
на ура не там Рамзан Ахматович построил
He forced the Russians to
русских он заставил
respect without We don’t
уважать без Ни нам без
care, we love people to take their Tajiks
разницы любим людей брать своих таджиков
Uzbeks Kyrgyz Uyghurs
узбеков кыргызов уйгуров
Chechens Inshe and everyone
чеченев инше и всех
else on
остальных на
Musul no one ever
мусуль никто ни кого никогда не обижает
offends anyone they tell them these skinheads
обижает они говорят их эти скинхеды
say that we came
говорить что мы приехали
there Moscow in general there are a lot of Nazis there my
там Москва вообще нацистов там очень
brothers and I  they came for a
много мы с братьями приезжали на
conversation and told you to teach
разговор рассказывали Ты научи пацанов
your boys how to lead the boys, teach yourself boys,
своих вести пацанов Научи себя пацаны
let them learn to behave well in the
Пусть научатся вести себя хорошо в
Stavropol Territory
Ставропольском крае
Okra where you have where you have presenting to
Окра где у тебя где у тебя предъява
which boy Tell the
какому пацану Говори номер
boy’s number You’re a smart guy I’m just telling you
пацана Ты же умный мужик я тебе просто
when on horseback I can’t tell you specifically
когда конно я не могу тебе конкретно
if Why are you why are you
сказать если Почему ты почему ты на
talking to the boys like that to our
пацанов говоришь так на нашего
brother because the guys say that the
брата потому что парни говорят
Stavropol boys are behaving badly the
Ставропольские что ведут плохо пацаны
Chechen boys Give me the number of the Stavropol
чеченские Дай номер Ставропольского
guy we will talk and ask
парня мы поговорим спросим
Why just little things Give your number about Yes
Зачем раз и мелочи Дай свой номер про Да
give the number You say that our Our brother is
дай номер Ты говори что наш Наш брат
behaving badly Ramzan  Akhmatovich
плохо себя ведёт Рамзан Ахматович
says if one of our people behaves badly,
говорит если кто-то из наших плохо себя
he punishes him; if someone
ведёт он его наказывает если кто-то
speaks badly about our brother and it’s
говорит плохо про наш брат и это
not true, he punishes him. Give him the number, we’ll
неправда Он наказывает его Дай номер мы
decide to punish our brother or punish him
решим наказать Наш брат или наказать
if he knew that you were sitting here on the phone
если бы знал что ты сидел тут в телефоне
and saying that.  with Christians and with the right But the
и говорил так с христианам и с право Но
body was You are Orthodox, you are Uzbek You are
те ло было Ты православный ты узбек Ты
Russian Come on, give me the
русский А ну дай
number Give me the number, give me the number I’ll
номер Номер дай дай номер я я тебя
take a picture of you
сфотографировать
now,
сейчас всё
come on Everything without
давай Всё без
work
работа
started marathon 100 with an ABC book
началось марафон 100 при книжка азбука
for Russians 100 karate techniques for
для русских 100 приёмов карате на
escaping
убегание
so first
так перший
everything went
шло всё
come on beauties, I'm from Gudermes Chechnya You're
давай красавицы я из Гудермес Чечня Вы
from Russia Belgorod region
откуда с России Белгородская области
Chechnya is also
Чечня - это тоже
Russia Belgorod region Belgorod Oh
Россия Белгородская область Белгород О
we were Belgorod Kursk we were standing there
мы были Белгород Курск были стояли там
now we're recovering in
сейчас восстанавливаемся в
Gudermes How old are you beauty
Гудермесе Сколько тебе лет красавица
who from
кому из
uh Well that's a
ээ Ну та что
beauty Who from we are both
красавица Кому из мы обе
beautiful saytan to
красивые сайтан
confuse  how old is your girlfriend What is your
попутать подружка твой сколько Как тебя
name and how
зовут и сколько тебе
old are you yes And how old do I look
лет ты да А на сколько выгляжу
19-20 The juice
19-20 Самый сок
in 3 weeks 20 more Oh this is your heart
через 3 недели 20 ещё О это тебе сердце
this is in 3 weeks I will be in the Belgorod
это через 3 недели я буду в Белгородской
region in 3 weeks I can
область через 3 недели Могу ээ подарок
bring some kind of gift  from Chechnya you want yes BMW
какой-то привезти из Чечни хочешь да BMW
M5
М5
f90 good Lip is not stupid but look at
f90 хорошая Губа не дура но посмотри на
yourself and look at BMW
себя и посмотри на BMW
BM oh
БМ ой
yin she want
йн она хотеть
BM
BM
And wait until then And who doesn’t want No well
А подожди вос А кто не хочет Не ну
without I’ll explain to you the point is that yes you
без я объясню тебе дело в том что да ты
want BMW
хотеть BMW
but are you worth it  BMW
но стоишь ли ты BMW
beauty Anyone anyone is worth a good
красавица Любой любой стоит хорошей
life a good car what's the problem or
жизни хороший машины в чём проблема или
someone looks or is worth some
кто-то выглядит или стоит какой-то
other car who wants something and
другой машины кто чего хочет того и
is worth it what's the problem Yes but it's like a market
стоит в чём проблема Да но это как базар
You come wanting to sell yourself for a BMW
Ты приходить хотеть продать себя за BMW
but no one is ready to pay  no wait,
но никто не готов заплатить нет подожди
what does it have to do with selling, every person
Причём тут продать у каждого человека
has their own desire, right, I’m not saying
есть своё желание правильно я не говорю
that someone gave me something I
чтобы мне кто-то чего-то там дарил Я
said my desire Like if it’s my
сказала моё желание Типа если это моё
desire I can do it myself as if I’m not
желание Я могу и сама на это как бы не я
I I asked what to give you  and you
я я спросил что тебе подарить а ты
say BMW X5 you're a little As they
говоришь BMW X5 ты немножко Как
say Well, who are you No no no
говорится Ну а кто ты такой Не не не
wait And who are you to give me anything
погоди А кто ты такой чтобы мне что-либо
I'm Akhmet from
дарить я Ахмет из
Gudermes Well
Гудермеса Ну
and what's your name
и А ты как тебя зовут
Eva Eve Oh I'll Adam Adam from
Ева Ева О я буду Адам Адам из
Eden I'll give  for you
Эдема Я подарю тебе
apple apple I don’t like apples I ione you
яблочко яблочко я не люблю яблоки я ione
mean
имеете в виду
iPhone Yes I don’t like
iPhone Да я не люблю
iPhone just BMW Well you don’t want a BMW
iPhone просто BMW Ну ты не тянуть на BMW
but I maybe not But there are some
а I можно да не А при тут какие-то
stereotypes here some people like a BMW some don’t
стереотипы кто-то тянет на BMW кто-то не
like  BMW or whatever you don’t want for now,
тянет на BMW или что ты пока не тянуть
I can give you an iPhone And
на ты я тебе могу подарить iPhone А
yours from your girlfriend
твоей от твоей подружки
Nokia
Nokia
[laughs]
[смех]
Thank you, give me an
Спасибо подари
X5, a window of opportunity has opened in life for my little one,
X5 у малой открылось в жизни окно
she finally found one that she’s
возможности она наконец нашла который ей
now just short in 3 weeks, and
сейчас прямо короче через 3 недели а
it’s good my friend is wearing a BMW  X5 full
хорошо подруга на тебе BMW X5 полной
set Oh damn, I can’t go further
комплекту Ой блин я не мож едем далее
healthy brother of
здоровом брат
subscribers How many subscribers do you have
подписчиков Сколько подписчиков у тебя
what kind of Subscriber I’m from Gudermes Chechnya
какой Подписчик Я из Гудермес Чечня ся
republic Where are you from
республика Ты откуда
and what are you Bor And I’m Akhmet from Gurme
а ты что такой Бор А я Ахмет из Гурме Ты
Where are you from
откуда
brother rme Yes and but they show Not this We
брат рме Да а а показывают Не это Мы
were in  We were stationed in the Kursk region
были в Курской область стояли мы ставим
so that we wouldn’t be detected
чтобы нас не засека
by direction finding Yes, where are you from,
пеленгация Да ты откуда
brother from there really? Where are you from, brother from there, the
оттуда реально Откуда ты брат
city is like that, what is Bor
оттуда город такой что такой Бор потому
because I’m
что я
a puppy And
щен А ты
who am I? I’m Russian Russian so you’re not a
кто я Я русский русский поэтому ты не
greyhound cleansing with a greyhound
борза очищение с борзой
always Hey, why are you saying that  give me the number
всегда Эй ты за что так говори дай номер
tomorrow we'll come over and talk Give your number
завтра подъедем поговорим Дай номер свой
come here Give me the number numbers Come on
сюда подъезжай Давай номер цифры Давай
brother and the number give me numbers numbers I'll give you
брат а номер давай циф цифры я тебе дам
let's
давай
dial 8 9 5 2 dial 8 9 5
давай 8 9 5 2 набираешь 8 9 5
2 3 68 3 6
2 3 68 3 6
further further
дальше
further further I won't
дальше дальше я те не
give you those yes I will  take a picture we will
дам да я тебя сфотографировать мы тебя
find you You are a Russian
найдём Ты русская
paka
пака
brother because the Russians are always afraid of the
брат потому что русские всегда боятся
Chechen Amadon
чеченца амадон
Sala their
Сала их
malya And I thought he would dictate the numbers to me
маля А я думал он продиктовать мне цифры
but he didn’t want to not want to afraid
но он не захотеть не захотеть боится
afraid Russian so go on brothers Oh
боится русский так ехать дальше братья О
Salam
Салам
aleikum aleikum salam I’m from Chechnya
алейкум алейкум салам Я из Чечня
Gudermes Where are you from
Гудермес Ты откуда
brother  I won’t tell you, brother,
брат не скажу брат я
the place where you are not allowed,
месте где тебе брат нельзя
brother, come on, tell me where you are. Why are
брат А ну давай говори где ты Почему ты
you so scared? I’ll tell you the secret of the company through the rocker arms, brother, are you so impudent, as you say, as a Chechen, I only understood from the bathhouse, brother, make sure you don’t go, you know, such a
смотри чтобы ты не пошл знаешь такая
bathhouse, a bathhouse  you know what a bathhouse is? Give me
баня баня знаешь что такая баня Дай
a number, give me a number, tomorrow we'll come and
номер дай номер завтра подъедем
tell you what a bathhouse is. Give me a
расскажет что такое баня Дай
number, get a bathhouse there at the Central Bank.
номер возьми там в Центробанке баня Дай
Give me a number. Central Bank got it. Give me a number here. Give me a number. I'll take a picture of you now. We'll take a picture of
Дай номер я тебя сейчас сфотографирую мы
you, dude, I'm
тебя чувак
banned.
забанился
I communicate with Dagestanis, that is,
Например я с дагестанцами общаюсь То
with people with children. They are more
бишь с людьми с детьми Они более
adequate than yours, wait, wait, wait,
адекватнее чем у подожди стой стой стой
more adequate than yours, you are yelling there,
более адекватнее чем у вас вы орёте там
Akhmat Sila, we are
Ахмат сила мы
Russia, Russia, like Akhmat Sila, yes,
Россию Россия как как Ахмат сила
girl, something go, give me the number here,
да Девушка что-то иди дай дай номер сюда
give the number, you are not
дай номер Ты не
ahma let me
ахма дай
go
ехать
further
дальше
Great I'm from Gudermes Chechnya Where are you
Здорово Я из Гудермес Чечня Ты
from Yes I'm from the
откуда Да я с
south Chechnya is also
юга Чечня тоже
south Stavropol oh I know we have brothers
юг Ставрополь о знаю у нас братья есть
Stavropol
Ставрополь
Mineralnye Vody yes yes Pyatigorsk Yes yes there are
Минеральные Воды есть да Пятигорск Да да
such cities there are such cities
есть такие города есть такие города
work they have a security
работа у них охранное
agency you
агентство ты
understand who you
понял ты кем
work brother  I work a lot Who do
работаешь брат я много Кем работаю ЧПУ
you know CNC What is a
знаеш Что такое
CNC machine something
ЧПУ станок чтото
CNC
ЧПУ
machine for free there is some kind of machine Well,
даре станок какой-то есть ти Ну ты
in short, the point is Got it Didn’t understand Well, this is a
короче суть Понял Не понял Ну это
working
рабочий
plant Dada yes it’s short in this area A
завод дада да это короче в этой сфере А
And we were here we were this Kursk region
А мы тут мы были это Курский область
Belgorod region now in  Gudermes
Белгородский область сейчас в Гудермес
we were taken to the re-
нас отвели на переу
manning station today we saw in Gudermes the
комплектовании сегодня видели в Гудермес
arrival
прилёт
was I don’t know the drone to fly to
был не знаю беспилотник долететь до
Gudermes We have a special forces institute here, there
Гудермеса У нас тут институт спецназа
is a university and there is Ramzan Akhmatovich
есть университет и там Рамзан Ахматович
to Listen, why am I watching you Ukraine is
до Слушай а чём тебя смотрю Украина друг
your friend Ukraine is yes we are when to be in the
у тебя Украина это да мы когда быть в
Kursk region we will put  VPN and I can’t
Курской область мы поставить VPN и я не
remove it, we put it so that we
могу убрать его мы ставить чтобы мы
stand near the borders so that we can stand where did you
возле границ стоять чтобы нас Куда ты
run away O Salam aleikum brother Aleikum
убежал О Салам алейкум брат Алейкум
salam o We returned Kursk region 3
салам о Мы вернулись Курский область 3
days ago now in Gudermes for re-
дня назад сейчас в Гудермесе на пере
equipment Where are you from brother
комплектация Ты откуда брат
city hero Volgograd o Volgograd is
город герой Волгоград о Волгоград есть
there  we are brothers they have there Business
там у нас братья у них там Бизнес есть
is a security
это охранный
agency tell me where you are not everywhere Our
агентство скажи где вас нету всюду Наш
brother is everywhere there is really a
брат всюду есть реально
million Chechnya there are a million people there is where
на миллион Чечня миллион люди есть куда
not to come everywhere Our brother is there and is
не приехать всюду Наш брат есть и всюду
respected everywhere Our
уважать Наш
brother and you are
брат а ты
not from
с не
Volgograd Why did you dress like a military man on a
Волгограде А что оделся как военный на
fishing trip  no, there’s nothing on fishing
рыбалке не это ничего нету на рыбалке
So why And so Why are you looking like a military man
Так почему А так Почему ты под военного
Dress up for fishing in a tracksuit
Оденься на рыбалку в спортивный костюм
like Well, we take off the nets so that we don’t
как Ну мы сети снимаем чтобы не запа
stop, we’re Chechens shedding blood for
стоп мы чеченцы кровь проливать за
Russia, we’re wearing military uniforms and
России мы военные формы ходить а
wearing military uniforms, that’s
находить воо
not it No insignia for sure Well,
не это Никаких знаков отличия точно Ну
show me  nothing no no no this is
покажи ничего нет не не не это это даже
n’t even Velcro You see that well, shaitan
липучки нету Ты видишь что ну шайтан
look if you deceive me
смотри если обманешь
Why don’t you go to
А почему не идёшь на
yours Well, let’s say with me
сво Ну у меня
Well, first of all, I have a reservation Well, I’m
скажем Ну во-первых у меня бронь Ну и
probably as old as you are 45
лет наверно мне уже сколько тебе лет 45
45 we have Akhmat Regiment  and 50 years of the EU up to 60
45 у нас Ахмат полк и 50 лет ЕС до 60
years to accept Ramzan
лет принимать Рамзан
Akhmatovich I drive fuel fuel I carry
Ахматович я топливо вожу топливо вожу
fuel al where the fuel is now look
топливо ал куда топливо сейчас смотри
Why we Chechens must defend Russia
Почему мы чеченцы должны защищать Россия
And you are a Russian sit I drive fuel Well, we
А ты русский сидить топливо вожу Ну мы
provide Well, how is the life of the country what kind of
обеспечиваем Ну как жизнь страны какой
armor are you? Give me the number tomorrow I will give it to you
ты броне го Дай номер завтра я передам у
on the shelves there is a mat of complete sets
на есть при полках мат комплектаций
the center is there they will call your Volgograd military registration and enlistment office
центр есть позвонят ваш военкомат
they will check or there is a reservation Give
Волгоград проверят или Есть бронь Дай
your number Why Well, I see you are a good
твой Зачем Ну я смотрю ты хороший
man Know how to wear a uniform You need to
мужчина Умей форма на тебе сидит нужно
protect the Motherland Why is our Chechen
Родина защищать Почему наш чеченский
brother shedding blood there And you
брат проливает кровь там А ты топливо
carry fuel, I can carry fuel too  Well, I
возить я тоже могу топливо возить Ну я
carry fuel Where do you transport fuel
топливо вожу Куда ты топливо возишь
rockets refuel
ракеты заправляют
what kind of oxidizer what is it let's
какой окислитель какой это давай там
land there we need to
посадку надо
storm fuel for rockets I'm coming it's
штурмовать топливо для ракет я приезжаю
worth installing Don't be nervous Don't
стоит установ Ты что ты не нервничай Не
stutter calmly brother I'm not yet Look I'm
заика спокойно брат я пока Смотри я пока
not talking harshly with you this is my
жёстко с тобой не говорю это у меня
way  just fuel
такая манера просто топливо Почему
Why Because when to say Russia for
Потому что когда говорить Россия для
Russians Moscow for Muscovites all Russian
русских Москва для москвичей все русские
dialect and when to defend Russia ku region
говор а когда защищать Россия ку область
regiment Akhmat Went Yes Belgorod region
полк Ахмат Пошёл Да Белгородский область
regiment Akhmat I didn’t see there very few
полк Ахмат Я не видел там очень мало
Russians there were Tatars yes Dagestan
русский был татары были да Дагестан
Isha it’s Buryats there were very few Russians
Иша это бурят был русских очень мало
Why  russian russian country there is a lot to
Почему русский русских страна много
protect why don't
защищать куда плеваться Ты что
you spit Are you a shaitan why are you at home I don't care I'm not at
шайтан ты почему себя дома Плевать я не
home what kind of house You don't care at your feet You're
дома какой дома Ты что ты себе под ноги
not at
плевать Ты что я не
home where are you
дома где ты
settings settings at home what kind of
настройки настройки у себя что за
construction Well you at home you where you are building there
стройка Ну ты у себя ты где строишь там
and
и
you spit Well, here’s a construction show show
плюёшь Ну а тут стройка покажи покажи
that this is a construction show that this is not a house it’s
что это стройка Покажи что это не дом
dark it’s Twist it Twist the camera show me
темно это Покрути Покрути камера покажи
I won’t show everything it means you
я не буду се показывать значит дома
’re sitting at home at home spat
сидишь дома плюнул
Oh okay come on
Эх ладно давай
Russians don’t
русский не
die just like Russians who die You
умирает как и русский умирает кто Ты
know a lot of Russians who died
много знаешь русских которые умерли
of course  of your friends,
конечно из твоих знакомых
how many of my friends are these, thank God,
сколько это из моих знакомых слава Богу
not many, but I have three brothers,
немного вот у меня у меня да Три брата
who died, one Zaporozhye
есть которые погибли один Запорожский
region and two Kursk region when
область и два Курский область когда
Ukraine was advancing and these are only brothers
Украина наступала а это только братья
Three brothers and more than 20 friends, this
Три брата а знакомых больше 20 это точно
will definitely be us and and what he did or  that you don’t need to
будет нас и и что сделал или что не надо
hang yourself, we need you to protect yourself, we can
повеситься надо чтобы ты на сво защит мы
protect you, and so we can, we need you to protect yours, I explained to you, I explained to you, I
защитил сво объяснил я тебе объяснил я я
drive fuel for rockets, are you or what, I don’t
вожу для ракет топлива ты или что не
understand Where in Volgograd for rockets fuel
пойму Где в Волгограде для ракет топлива
rockets are different for us Where in  In
ракеты на сво у нас разни Где в
Volgograd, we have to carry fuel on our own, there is
Волгограде топливо у нас на сво надо
not enough driver, there is a mechanic, there is a
возить не хватает водитель механик есть
driver, there is not enough fencing, we have an oil refinery in the city,
водитель не хватает ограде у нас в граде
you know about
нефтеперерабатывающий завод ты знаешь об
this, I know a lot, we have an
этом я знаю много у нас
oil refinery in Russia
нефтеперерабатывающий завод в России
where there is also Anapa and I, my
есть где есть и Анапа есть и я у меня
friends were in Novorossiysk  there is
друзья были в Новороссийск там есть
shipping there Yes, there was oil there, it’s not a plant, it’s
отгружать Да была нефть там не завод же
not a plant there, but we have a plant or a
там же не завод А у нас завод есть или
terminal. I don’t understand these options and that’s all
терминал Я не понимаю эти варианты и всё
I know. I have a reservation, I carry
я те гою Уменя У меня есть бронь я вожу
fuel for rockets or something, maybe not enough,
топливо для ракет что мало что ли мало
well, not enough, Why?  so let the Chechens
разве Ну мало Почему так пусть чеченцы
carry Let the Chechens carry and the Russian goes to
возят Пусть чеченцы возят а русский идёт
defend himself, this is Russia, your Motherland
защититься это ж Россия ваша Родина
Rurik founded
Рюрик там ещё основал
it there all all all you oh you put on a
её все все все ты о ты одел шапку
Wagner hat And you were in Wagner if you didn’t
Вагнера А ты в вагнере был если ты не
fight why did you why the
воевал зачем ты зачем
rear How do you
тыл Откуда ты
know they were in ours  There are
знаешь были были в наш Курской область
few of them in the Kursk region, but they
мало их но
were from where do you know?
были откуда ты знаешь А ты почему ты
And why do you know why
почему не вагнере А откуда ты знаешь был
you weren’t in Wagner? And how do you know whether I was or not you weren’t in Wagner because
я или нет не был ты в вагнере потому что
you’re not a child’s Wagner is visible in the eyes
ты ты не детский Вагнер по глазам видно
but not visible, here’s Wagner - This is a good warrior
а не видно вот Вагнер - Это хороший воин
Because  so the Russians are some kind of cowards
Потому что так русские какие-то трусы
Shakata Wagner he is not afraid he really
шаката Вагнер он не боится он реально
was we were Neighbors in the sector with Wagner and
был мы были Соседи на секторе с Вагнер а
they hold the sector very well when we
они очень хорошо держат сектор мы когда
retreated they were still standing and retreated later Yes there
отошли они ещё стояли и отошли позже Да
are these are my brothers Why not why did you
есть это мои братья Почему не почему ты
wear a military insignia you said  that there is no
одел шеврон военного ты говорил что нет
insignia This is an insignia Yes, I’ll
знако отличия Это знак отличия Да я тебя
take a picture of you I’ll take a picture of you
сфотографирую я сфотографирую что ты
[laughter]
[смех]
this is at the stage of photography they have such a
это на этапе фотографии у них такой
maximum drain
максимальный слив
chiefly wearing a
главно одел
cap damn I’m drowning I’m drowning I have a reservation I’m
кепка блин топлю топлю у меня бронь Я
drowning my hands
топлю руки
are shaking
трясутся
the armored car itself
броневик сам
alaikum Wa alaikum assalam oh Bra Brother I
алейкум Ва алейкум ассалам о Бра Брат я
from Gudermes Chechnya Where are you from
из Гудермес Чечня Ты откуда
brother Gudermes yes And where are you
брат Гудермес да А ты
from the Altai Territory o Barnaul
откуда Алтайский край о Барнаул
I have brothers in Barnaul they run a
у меня братья есть Барнауле они там
security agency there
охранное агентство
for example Hello and also
держат допустим Здравствуй и ещё
Gornoaltaisk But this is a different subject It seems like
Горноалтайск Но это другой субъект Вроде
this is a republic there too there are brothers
это да республика там тоже е есть братья
What are you talking about here
А о чём общаешься тут
brother
брат
again  I was in the Kursk region, we were
раз я он был в Курской области нас
taken to re-staffing now in
отвели на пере укомплектование сейчас в
Gudermes Today we had an arrival, I saw
Гудермесе Сегодня у нас прилёт был видел
the news Well, two dots
новость А ну две точечки
on the University
на Университете
lit up a little, yes, but it’s unpleasant
загорелись немножко было да но неприятно
anyway that
всё равно что к нам прилетело как-то
somehow two dots flew to you Barnaul just to
так две точечки к тебе Барнаул просто к
Barnaul doesn’t reach you It’s very
тебе не долетает Барнаул Это очень
far Barnaul
далеко Барнаул
I understand I saw I
я понял я я видел видел
saw and there
видел а на с
was God dear Why don’t you go
был бог милого А почему не идёшь
defend your
защитить
homeland I have someone to protect from
родину мне есть Кого защищать у
me wait Why do we
меняя подожди Почему мы
defend Russia And you’re Russian You’re
защищать Россия А ты русский Ты
Russian And you’re what a
русский А ты какой я
Chechen I am You’re Russian
чеченец Ты русский
I this is what it means this
я это что значит это
Wars Chechen
Войнах чеченец
Nokhchi
нохчи
Yeah we Why why Nokhchi is us We
Ага мы Почему почему нохчи это нас Мы
call ourselves that Nokhchi Russians call
так называют себя нохчи русски называть
us Chechen in Russian Chechen in the army
нас чеченец по-русски чеченец по войски
noche Yeah why don’t you know
ноче Ага ты почему не знаешь
yours And why should I be on s
своего А почему мне я должен быть на с А
Why don’t you  I was my own, I’m telling you,
почему ты не на сво я ж был Я же говорю
3 days ago, bring us back to the
У нас 3 дня назад привести назад на
manning lane, brothers are
переу комплектования братья есть
wounded, all the wounded brothers are wounded,
раненые весь раненый братья есть раненые
our regiment was returned to the manning lane.
нас полк вернули на переу комплектование
Why don’t you go to
Ты почему не на
yours, there’s something wrong. Why don’t you go to yours?
сво ты что-то брешь Ты почему не на сво
Give me the number of something-  then give me your number
Дай номер что-то ты бь дай номер свой
tomorrow they will call you in
завтра позвонят тебе в
Barnaul and help you draw up a contract Give me the
Барнаул помогут оформить контракт Давай
city code
код города
3852 Come on Give me the
3852 Давай на Давай
number 3852 I’ll tell you the city code and
номера 3852 я тебе говорю код города а
then Well, somehow you yourself say
дальше Ну как-то сами ты же говоришь
Call me the city code and so yes I’ll
Позвони я вам код города и так да я
take a photo of
сейчас сфотографирую
you now  Let's do it like this Oh
тебя Давай вот так Ах
thy Now I'll dial
тый Сейчас я наберу
brother
брат
bale we've settled everything, we'll find you brother Everything's
бале мы всё уладил найдём тебя брат Всё
settled, let's talk I think that you
уладил поговорим Я думаю что ты
talk differently about yours, you need to
по-другому говорить про сво надо
defend your homeland, you need to defend your homeland, because the
защищать надо Родина защитить потому что
homeland is not only a Chechen, a Russian
Родина - это не только чеченец русский
must go to fight, I
должен идти воевать
also understand, of course, come on  Of course, you can
тоже понял конечно давай Конечно номер
tell us the number so that we can find you easier.
скажешь чтобы мы тебя легче найти быть А
How is it? Busik can you send the number to
как там это Бусик может пришлёшь номер
tell me? Let’s send you
сказать мне Давай мы тебе пришлём и
Busik and Musick and Pusik, let’s send
Бусик и Мусик и Пусик давай пришлём всё
you everything you need, tell me the
тебе что надо скажи
number. Yes, why are you doing that?
номер Да зачем ты так всё
Tell me the number, I say. Come on.
вы номер сказать номер те говорю Давай
yourself Calculate Let's say the
ты сам Вычисли Давай сказать
number yourself alaikum
номер сам алейкум
dachshund
таксу
brother No not taksuyu What are you from Chechnya Where are you
брат Нет не таксую Ты из какой Чечня Ты
from
б из
Russia too Russia
Росси тоже
asked I'm from Russia too Moscow I
Россия даскал Я из России тоже Москва Я
said How are you doing there
сказал Как у вас там дела
those pronunciation is not the same what's the difference
те произношение не такое какая разница
Well it's only nights to the feet maybe so
Ну это только ночи к ног может так
contact Why Who said I communicate
обращаться Почему Кто сказал я общаюсь
very much I
очень
like many friends there is no need to
нравится много друзей не надо
parody our
пародировать наш
language Why I don’t parody your language Your
язык Почему у тебя я не пародирую У тебя
sound is accented I have a very unpleasant Russian accent
звук акцентом у меня русский акцент у
Well okay who are you working
Ну хорошо ты кем работаешь
brother I don’t work all the best I’m
брат я не работаю всего хорошего я
further E not al You  why not on s Yes you
дальше Э не ал Ты почему не на с Да ты
Why this sami
Поче этот самы
cut out alaikum bra alaikum Alam I see
выпилил алейкум бра алейкум Алам я вижу
our
наши
brothers the region is
братьях облас
also s on
тоже с на
restored You are from where are you from
восстановлено Вы откуда ро откуда
Moscow
Москва
Muscovites
москвичи
Muscovites I have
москвичи Я за 3 года с не одного
n’t seen a single Muscovite in the Kursk region in 3 years and
Москвича не видел в Курской области и в
unfortunately they don’t
Белгородской к сожалению не
send them to Belgorod region  I mean, no, you weren’t navo, I’m
отправляют в смысле не ты не наво
not,
был я нет
where are you
где ты
then
тогда
Moscow Why am I a Chechen defending Russia And
Москва Почему я чеченец защищаю Россия А
you don’t defend from Moscow
ты из Москвы не защищаешь
because I’m protecting the Sky of
потому что я охраняю Небо
Moscow Why Muscovites don’t go to fight why for
Москвы Почему москвичи не идут воевать
Moscow you don’t defend the heart of Russia you go to
Москва сердце России не защищаешь идёшь
with you defend you go to with because  that I am
в с защищаешь идёшь в с потому что я
protecting the heart of Russia and not going to
защищаю сердце России а не иду на
my own understanding, that is, you are cowards, I understand, I understand.
сво понял то есть вы трусы я понял понял
Well, you know, when Akhmat is the first to flee from the
Ну знаешь когда Ахмат первый бежит с
battlefield, you call me a coward. Akhmat is
поля боя ты меня трусом называешь Ахмат
from the battlefield. Give me the number. Give me the number. Let’s
с поля боя Дай номер Дай номер
talk. Tomorrow we’ll talk. The manager
пообщаемся Завтра пообщаемся зав
will come to you with representatives of the Akhmad regiment.
подъедут представители полка Ахмад к вам
some of them will talk they say you will tell them in your
в часть поговорят говорят скажешь им в
eyes you will tell them in your eyes Give me the
глазах скажешь им в глазах Давай номер
number Give me the number, write it down
Давай номер записывай Давай
Come on 8
давай 8
986 12
986 12
07 441
07 441
Why did you react
Почему ты так отреагировал
to him like that Let me
на него Дайте я вас на всякий случай
take a photo of you just in case Bring it back here Why were you
сфотографирую Верни сюда Почему ты
scared Give
испугался Дай
me someone else’s number name Let’s say it to your
сюда чужой номер назва Давай скажешь в
face  regiment Akhmat circus Yes You say to run away
глаза полк Ахмат цирк Да Скажешь убегать
we already had one like that and we have one like that
уже был один такой у нас н такой у нас
come here come
давай сюда давай
here give your face here Show the faces here Show the faces here
сюда дай лицо сюда Покажи лиц сюда
Show Look into the eyes of the Chechen, look
Покажи Посмотри в глаза чеченцу посмотри
into the eyes of the
в глаза
Nts Tomorrow we’ll talk to your commander
нцу завтра с вашим командиром поговорим
and you’ll apologize for
да и это будешь извиняться За
Akhmat while we’re at it  We have three brothers who
Ахмат пока мы кро у нас три братья
were killed, this is the Kursk region and you
полегло это Курский область а ты
say that you should run away, say that you should run away.
говоришь что убегать говори что убегать
Gourmet, they will bring you here to Gudermes, I
Гурме тебя привезут сюда в Гудермес
will show you to the brothers, you will go through and tell
покажу ты братьям пройдёшь и скажешь
everyone that you should run away, and you will say
всем что убегать да каждому в глаза
it to everyone’s face.  I’ll
сюда лицо покажи цка я тебя
take a picture of
сфотографирую
her that they’re so afraid
ней что они так боятся
oh-oh a Take a picture of you I’m
ой-ой а Сфотографировать тебя у меня
recording in progress I’m recording the case I’m
запись идёт запись я делаю запись дела Я
already cunning I’m you now if you don’t
уже хитрый Я тебя сейчас если не
take a picture I’ll record you’re
сфотографировать у меня записывать ты
in trouble recording you’re in trouble Minor You
попал малой записывать ты попал Малой Ты
already have the
уже у тебя есть
opportunity to either apologize and say that
возможность либо извиниться сказать что
you are mistaken or tomorrow we will
ты ошибся либо завтра будем через
decide through the command command to
командование решать командование
decide
решать
[laughter]
[смех]
like the second
с типа второй
time there is nothing Russian Yes
раз ничего нет русского Да
soldier Where are you from I am from Russia and Chechnya is
солдатик Ты откуда Я из России а Чечня
also Russia or don’t you think Russia
тоже Россия или ты что не считаешь Росси
Chechnya is not me just from Moscow Nuna Moscow
Чечня не я просто из Москвы Нуна Москва
Usta Moscow Gudermes Chechnya What  Ukraine Are
Уста Москва Гудермес Чечня Какая Украина
you showing me that you are from
Ты что меня показывается что ты из
Ukraine And this is a VPN We were in the Kursk
Украины А это VPN Мы были в Курской
region We installed a VPN so that we can’t and
области Мы ставили VPN чтобы нас не и не
can’t be changed in roulettes now it’s standing And the same thing is the same thing too
може поменять в рулетках теперь стои А
yes Course we are
то же самое тоже самое тоже да Курс мы
now we returned 3 days ago to the re-
сейчас мы вернулись 3 дня назад на переу
acquisition  because there are many wounded
комплектования потому что раненых много
and you are now on your way
а ты сейчас на сво
Well, for now 3 days ago we
Ну на сейчас 3 дня назад мы в Гурме
arrived back in Gurma, now we are
приехали назад сейчас нас
repairing our cars and our brothers are treating us, we will
чиним автомобили и лечат братья будем
go again in 2 weeks And
через 2 неделя ехать снова А тебе
how old are you brother, I turned 18, too,
сколько лет брат мне 18 исполнилось тоже
you are going to your place soon, not first to the
идёшь на сво скоро не сначала в
university
университет
at the university he is 18 years old, he is going to defend Russia and
униве 18 лет он идёт защищать России а
you are going to learn this I have an illness I am not
ты идёшь учить это у меня болезнь я не
drafted I have bronchial asthma I
призывной у меня астма бронхиальная не
can’t what is bronchial Asma Akhmat strength
могу что бронхиальна асма Ахмат сила
they take any Asma not Asma we can
берут любая асма не асма мы можем тебе
do it for you you will sit not run
сделать ты будешь сидеть не бегать
automatic And sit at the headquarters to lead the Drone
автомат А сидеть в штаб руководить Дрон
with asthma you can manage Drone But I didn’t
с астмой можно Дрон руководить А я не
know, well, you need to think then yes Give the
знал ну то надо подумай тогда да Давай
number tomorrow We’ll help you think
номер завтра Поможем тебе подумать
Hello guy thought very quickly and made the
Алло тип очень быстро подумал и принял
right decision to leave salaam alaikum
правильное решение слинять салам алейкум
alaikum Oh handsome guys, where are you from?
алейкум О красавчики Вы откуда
Brothers from Moscow I’m from Gourmet What are you
братья из Москвы Я из Гурме Что ты руку
holding your hand you want to switch  or that the
держишь хочешь переключить или что
Chechen immediately switches not for me, it’s
чеченца сразу переключаешься не у меня
just, well, my hand is automatically set to
просто ну у меня автоматом рука стоит на
switch, take your hand from the EU So are you
переключение забери руку ЕС Так что
afraid of me or Yes, I’m from Gudermes Chechnya for
боишься меня или Да я из Гудермес Чечня
you How old are you students I look yes yes
вам по Сколько лет вы студенты смотрю да
yes for 20 for 20 for But you’re dressed in
да да по 20 по 20 по А вот вы одели
military  hat Why don’t you go to fight
военный шапка А почему не идёте воевать
Why, well, here I am and my brothers Akhmat, we
А зачем ну вот я и мои братья Ахмат мы
defend the Kursk region, Belgorod
защищать Курский область Белгородский
region, we are going back to Gudermes for
область мы вот вернуться в Гудермес на
restoration now 3 days ago in
восстановлении сейчас 3 дня назад через
2 weeks again and I don’t go military
2 недели снова и я не ходить военный
hat and
шапка и
antlers to do yes in front of the girl in front of
панты делать да перед девочко перед
the boy  Why are you here like a military man and
мальчик Да что ты тут типа военный а
don’t want to fight, we are, well, we study at the
повоевать не хоти мы это ну мы учимся на
military department, these are the hats from there, military
военной кафедре это шапки оттуда военный
cafe You
кафе Ты
know, you’re tired, you know, when you can
знаешь ты устал знаешь ты когда можно
wear it, when you can’t, there’s something to eat there, Tue tape
носить когда нельзя там есть что Вт
measure, you can go out Like this in a hat and
рулетка можно выходить Вот так в шапка и
a T-shirt No, I don’t know  you're a disgrace to the
футболка Нет не знаю ты позоришь форма
Russian military uniform, let me
российский военный дай я тебя
take a picture of you, what are you
сфотографирую что ты скипа что ты
saying, skipa, what are you saying, skipa, I'll sleep you now,
говоришь скипа я тебя сейчас
they put on caps to show off here,
спну они одели шапочки понтоваться тут
look for Ukrainians
украинцев пошукай
Yes, you're 18 years old, you
Да 18 лет есть тебе
look to me 43, I just don't
выглядишь мне 43 Просто я с дети не
tell the kids I'm from Gourmet Chechnya Where are you from? I'm from
говорить я из Гурме Чечня Ты откуда Я из
Belgorod  Oh, we were just in Kursk,
Белгородом О мы были как раз Курск
Belgorod, we returned 3 days ago, the power steering of
Белгород мы 3 дня назад вернулись ГУР
local restoration, in two weeks
местного восстановления через два недели
we are going back. How are you now? 3 days are
едем назад Как там у вас сейчас 3 дня
calm 3 days are still calm
спокойно 3 дня пока что спокойно
Yes, you don’t want to help us too, so that not
Да ты не хотеть тоже помочь нам чтобы не
only luck And also your help
только удача А ещё твоя помощь
Yes  wanted to help m Give me the number, we
был Да хотел помочь м Дай номер мы
will transfer our Belgorod military registration and enlistment office
передадим наш военкомат Белгородский
where
куда Салам
Salaam alaikum ma Aleikum assalam o What kind of flag do
алейкум ма Алейкум ассалам о Что за флаг
you have
у тебя
interesting interesting yes forty neck brigade
интересно интересно да сорок шея бригада
Oh sconce Yes where are you
О бра Да где
standing I already know how long I haven’t been standing damn it
стоите Я уже знаешь сколько не стою блин
for 10 10 10 years we we we regiments mat
уже лет во 10 10 10 мы мы полках мат
we returned now Kursk region 3 days
вернулись сейчас Курский область 3 дня
ago and what kind of flag do you have, the Chechen
назад а у тебя что за флаг э чеченский
Republic we have now returned from the
республика мы сейчас вернулись из
Kursk region to Gudermes on
Курской область в Гудермес на
recovery 3 days later 2 days and two
восстановлении 3 дня через 2 дня и два
weeks we are going to
неделя едем снова на
Kursk again Wait, but we have a Chechen one, a
Курск Подожди а у нас же чеченская
little different green And this
немножко другой зелёный был А это Потому
Because now you have a Kadyrov Republic
что сейчас у вас республика кадыровская
And this is the Chechen Republic of Ichkeri and a
А это Чеченская республика ичкери а
real Chechen is a real Che and come on
настоящий чечен настоящий че а ну давай
tell me no I just wanted SBO let’s
расскажи не не я просто хотел СБО
talk why is the boy lying now
поговорим а зачем мальчик сейчас брешет
and why is the boy now and you weren’t there
а зачем мальчик сейчас а вы не были там
but because my friends were there and  they are
а потому что мои друзья там были и они
there now, why are
сейчас там есть зачем
you not listening? We are standing, we are holding the Kursk
ты ты не слышишь Мы стоим мы курскую
region, we are holding your Russians, there are no Russians there,
область держим ваших русских нету там
my guys, the Kursk region,
область мои ребята Курская область там
who is dying there, we are a regiment, hma
поды кто подыхает там ны полка хма
don-don, we suffered losses there, the Russians
дон-дон мы там несли потери русские
ran away on the first day, what are you
убежали ещё в первый день Да что ты
saying?  what are you saying? Tell
говоришь Да что ты говоришь Рассказывай
me, then come on, look me in the eyes,
давай тогда глаза мне посмотри в глаза
look me in the eyes and say good-bye. Come on. Let’s
мне посмотри и скажи дой день Давай
talk. Your husband is also
Давай разговаривать твой муж тоже
hiding here, he’s not going to his place, he’s been hiding for
прячется тут он не идёт на сво прячется
8 years, he’s saying he’s not coming. Why are you
8 лет говорит не идёт Зачем ты Зачем ты
interrupting a woman when you’re being dismantled
перебиваешь женщину когда вас разбирали
because look in the eyes?  if you
потому что смотри в глаза если ты
talk to me in the eyes, look at your
говорить со мной в глаза посмотри твой
husband now, he’ll switch, he’s a coward, I don’t understand in
сейчас муж переключится трус я не пойму
any way. Why are you interrupting, I wo
никак Зачем ты перебиваешь я
n’t switch because you
переключаться не буду потому что ты в
won’t look me in the eye, look into my eyes, I’ll
глаза не смотришь Посмотри в глаза я
listen to you.
тебя выслушаю
Yes, listen here, explain to me why.
Да Слушай сюда объясни мне зачем же
Good. That’s a good speaker, Hello, because  that I
Хорош Вот орач хорош Алло потому что я
was there in the Kursk region We stood
был там в Курской области Мы стояли
holding the border While your husband was
держали границу Пока твой муж тут
resting here there was a man under your skirt, the corpses
отдыхал у тебя под юбкой человек трупов
were mine Stop it, how many of yours
было моих Прекрати мац Сколько твоих там
died there, not a single Russian died there
погибло ни один русский не погиб там у
we’re talking, wait, talk
наша разговариваю подожди разговаривай
to me
со мной
Please wait Why why is she
Пожалуйста подожди Почему почему она
so childish  Why exactly on the day I
такая дет Почему именно в день вот я
want to ask you a question Why exactly on the
хочу тебе вопрос задать Почему именно в
day when there was a
день когда был
Heavy battle There was a heavy battle Akhmat’s
на Тяжёлый бой был Тяжёлый бой через
troops were withdrawn through Oryol
Орёл вывели немного войск
you were there to
Ахмата ты там был чтобы такое
say this I’ll say now Yes he was there you
говорить я скажу сейчас Да он там был ты
know where I was Where you were Where  I was he was
знаешь где я был Где ты был Где я был он
n’t shining Believe me, he was Where Akhmat was taken out
не светил Повери был Где Ахмат выводили
where you were you’re sitting there at home under your skirt
где ты был ты сидишь там дома под юбкой
married that’s all And we And now
жената свой вот и всё А мы А теперь
listen to me
слушай меня
carefully be silent And now listen to me
внимательно молчи А теперь слушай меня
carefully I was in one place in the
внимательно Я был в одном месте в
only good place you know where
единственном хорошем месте знаешь где
there where  Akhmat was just shut up
там где Ахмат был как раз таки помолчи
please know where I was where you
пожалуйста знаешь где я был где ты
were you should say something like these
был тебе что-нибудь говорить такие
names of cities point Martan
названия городов очко Мартан
And you want to say that you were once
А ты хочешь сказать что ты был когда-то
in
в
Chechnya you see that just like that here
Чечне видиш что просто так вот здесь
behind the square a minute more Remember
сзади площадь минутка ещё Вспомни
shut up now
помолчи теперь
further  so look, we are you shaitans
дальше так вот смотри мы вас шайтанов
Then Ishma then for mincemeat
Тогда ишма тогда на фарш
we are defending Russia you escaped through Orel
мы защищаем Россию вы убежали через Орёл
Akhmat the wounded were taken out because Akhmat
Ахмат раненых вывозили потому что Ахмат
Rakhmet we were on the first line of
Рахмет были мы были на первой линии
battle And you were where there I didn’t see you
борьбы А вы были где там я тебя не видел
in the Kursk region not my former friend
в Курской область не былой мой друг
Shut up he  prays to speak again
Помолчи он молится ещё раз говорить
someone I will tell you your your woman
кто-нибудь я тебе скажу твоя твоя баба
commands you You are not a man your
тобой командует Ты не мужчина твоя
woman your woman screams about you she
женщина твой кричит о тебя она для тебя
understood nothing for you you you
ничто поняла ты ты
daughter
доч
understood the rumors you are
поняла слы ты уже
no longer behaving like that you
не так себ не ведёт ты
tykh Akhmed you we we Akhmat we keep
тых Ахмед ты мы мы Ахмат мы держать
Kursk region you don’t keep Kursk region
курски область ты не держать курски обла
Jam and you will be received here Jumbo and yours come to
Джам а теб здесь примут Джамбо иваш ко
me here you are Give me a number Give
мне вот ты Давай номер Давай номер Дава
me a number Let me accept you You
мне тебя примет вот этого флага у вас
definitely
точно
don’t have this flag Give me a number baby Give me your number
нет Давай номер малышка Дай номер мы
tomorrow and we’ll ask who came out of Orel
завтра и мы спросим кто выходил из Орла
Come on
Давай
Look in  in all
Посмотри во всех
respects you because you know that
отношениях вы потому что вы знаете что
Akhmat Akhmat Yes, we keep everything you Russians
Ахмат Ахмат Да мы держать всё вы русские
don’t want to fight for yours Russia we
не хотите воевать за свой Россия мы
Akhmat fight for you
Ахмат воевать за вас
[laughter]
[смех]
That woman was
Вот это баба была
under this
под это
fire, switch off, you’ve already switched off
огонь отключайся ты уже отключился
[music]
[музыка]
since you can switch yourself and not
раз можешь сама переключиться и не
turn on
включаться
please
пожалуйста
turn off I'm usually a Russian boy Chen here
отключается я обычно русский бои Чен тут
I'm a Chechen they're afraid of you Russian woman
я чеченец тебя русскую бабу
It's me you it's you what's
бояться Вот это я тебя это ты чего там
that doing this spell I'll conjure you I'll
это этот колдуешь я тебя наколдую
conjure you your face is already coded they're
колдую твоё лицо уже закодовано меня
already afraid of me Dasha
боятся уже тако Даша
[music]
[музыка]
will leave 100 times more than she wants
уйдёт в 100 раз больше чем она желает
let
пусть
Chachacha go and you won’t get anything, it
Чачача а ничего у тебя не получи
will work out
получится
you fell Yes you
тебя Да ты
fell Everything you see is already falling it
упал Всё видишь у тебя уже падают это
fell on you because your phone
легло на тебя потому что твой телефон
fell
упал
from the woman for real The phone fell and Anro didn’t
у бабы реально Телефон упал а анро не
win baby your
выиграл малышка тебе
heart is mine my heart is yours too  I'm
сердце мне сердце а тебе тоже сердце я
from Chechnya You're
изме Чечня Ты
from
откуда
Moscow Moscow Oh you're what's your name My
Москва Москва Ой ты как тебя зовут Меня
name is
зовут
VRT she's name Come on Why is
е зовут ВРТ она е зовут А ну дай Почему
he making faces like that Give me this
он так кривляется Дай сюда этого
impudent guy here I'll talk to him
дерзкого я с ним поговорю
now I'll take a picture of you I
сейчас я тебя сейчас я сфотографирую Я
took a picture of him
сфотографировал его
Come on now give me the number Give me the number  I’ll
Давай давай теперь номер давай номер я
drive up and talk to him and I’ll come up to talk
подъеду поговорю а я подъеду поговорить
to him because he’s grimacing against me,
с ним потому что он кривляется против
I took a picture of him, we’ll
я его сфотографировал мы его
hire him to find him faster Come
найм чтоб быстрее найти Давай
on, what’s your
да как вас
name Veronica Veronica My name is Akhmed,
зовут Вероника Вероника Меня зовут Ахмед
I’m from Gurmechnya You’re from
я из Гурме чня Ты откуда
Veronica I’m Akhmet from Gudermes Chechnya you’re
Вероника я Ахмет из Гудермеса Чечня ты
Veronica from where
Вероника откуда
from A  not ahd but Akhmed Chechnya
откуда А не ахд а Ахмед Чечня
r Hey Bearded Man Go make Veronica some coffee
р Эй Бородач Иди сделай Веронике кофе
Let me know Nasko has brothers
Давай знаю у Наско братья есть
Yes this is my
Да это мой
husband Go do it Veronica
муж Иди сделай Веронике
will
му будет
always go ahead and leave my husband in the other direction
всегда вперёд уйти мужу в другую сторону
and I’ll tell you what you want Give me
а я тебе говорить ты хочешь дай дай
the phone Give me the phone I’ll come and talk
телефон Дай телефон я подъеду поговорю
if you  something you object
если ты что-то возражаешь
Give the number Give the number tell me with I'm
Дай номер дай номер скажи с я те
taking pictures in
фотографирую
your number Give the number I'll come tomorrow
вй номе Дай номер я подъеду завтра
I'll talk to Maykop this day I'll be
поговорю до Майкопа это день буду
at drive up address skaz Let's talk
по подъезжай адрес сказа Давай говори
talk Write the Republic of
говори Пиши республика
Agea
агея
Tax Raon
такс раон
so village Nabo so so Yampolskogo street
так село набо так так улица ямпольского
so so
так так
26 because  the guy on the street has become
26 потому что тип на улице стал
cheerful, show me
бодрый покажи
tomorrow, I'll be there tomorrow after lunch, I'll
завтра буду завтра после обеда буду
be there in the morning, we'll leave in the morning. Well, I'll show you your passport. Well, show me your
выедем Ну паспорт покажу ре Ну покажи
passport. Let me talk to your little guy
паспорт Давай я с твоим мужичков
one on one.
поговорим один на один
Come on, this is the face that's just you, what are you
давай это лицо которое просто ты что ты
hanging out with, what are you waiting for now, tomorrow
тусуешься что ты подожди сейчас завтра
we'll come up, we need to be responsible for our
подъедем надо отвечать за свой
market  you're not going to go now to the girl
базар не ты сейчас будешь ехать девушке
Yes, come to me, I'll come tomorrow with you, my
Да приедь ко мне я приеду завтра с тобой
brothers and I will take you, I'll talk to you, I'll
мы с братьями пори брать я с тобой я с
talk to the girl Let's come to me
девушкой поговорю Давай ко мне
Well, damn, what's the difference? Oh,
идёт Ну блин а разница в чём же аре Ой
what a Shotik Oh what legs,
какой Шотик О какие ножки
well, I don't care  I gave the same address correctly
ма ну я всё равно же адрес верно дала
What difference does it make? What
Какая разни
difference do you make? What are you sitting down? Man
что разница Ты что Ты что на сел Мужик
Hey Give me everything Tomorrow we will come brothers
Эй Дай всё Завтра мы приедем братья
will talk to you Me and the girl
поговорят с тобой я с девушкой
Salaam alaikum girls don’t Aley don’t
Салам алейкум девушки не Алей не
switch don’t be afraid I’m
переключайтесь не бойтесь я
kind even though I’m not scared of you I’m from
добрый яже вроде не испуг вых Я из
Gudermes they just see me  beard and
Гудермес просто меня видят борода и
switch I'm from Gudermes Chechnya You're
переключаться Я из Гудермес Чечня Вы
from here And we're from here Oh how daring
откуда А мы отсюда Ох дерзкий
What's your name so brave and
какой Как тебя зовут такую смелую
daring You
дерзкую
won't believe it for a laugh I'm not called
не поверите чисто поржать Меня не зовут
I came to you myself
я сама пришла к вам
Wah you l sticks Yes Sticks Fir trees is also the
Вах ты л палки Да Палки Ёлки тоже
history of all folk ska Where are you from
история всего народных ска Откуда ты
say Yes I  from our moronic region of
скажи Да я с дебильного нашего края
Donbass where we are all a little bit of that
Донбасса где мы все чуть-чуть того
daring extreme, but I was from the Kursk region
дерзкие крайние та я с Курской области
Donbass was not there brothers were
был Донбасс не был там братья были
Donbass Vete Donetsk people I can smell that And
Донбасс Вете Донецкие люди Чучу того А
you are now in Donetsk Yes, of course I can,
вы сейчас в Донецке Да конечно могу всё
we all have to We are now in Gudermes for
нас должны Мы сейчас в Гудермесе на
restoration later  Kursk I can
восстановление потом Курске вас могу в
come to Donetsk instead of
Донецк приехать вместо
Kursk It all depends on the desire where I
Курск Всё зависит от желания куда есть я
already wish I
уже желаю я вас
wish you I don’t need to wish I am not a reward
желаю меня желать не надо я я не награда
I’m heavenly punishment no no no no need to wish
я кара небесная не не не не надо желать
this is your girlfriend and you have the
это ваш подружка а у вас есть
opportunity to wish
возможность пожелать
Yes wish I
Да пожелать
wish you  but not for yourself Because I feel
Желаю вам но не себя Потому что мго
sorry for you As they say, don’t covet the girlfriend of the
жалко Как говорится не возжелай подружку
girl you
девушки которую ты
coveted oh-oh-oh what a deep
возжелал ой-ой-ой какие глубокие
knowledge of the Koran probably or what isn’t this,
познания Корана наверное или чего не это
we have a Chechen joke, it
у нас чеченский шутка есть
can be like that, but we know how it is
такой может быть а у нас знаете как есть
People’s Joke not Yes, not executed  there
Народная Шутка не Да не казнён
will be such a Folk Donetsk proverb,
будеш такая Народная Донецкая поговорка
it’s cool, well, in Donetsk you
прикольно ну в Донецке у вас там этих
don’t have these guys left there anymore, our guys,
мужиков уже не осталось там наши ребята
I
я
know No, thank God we have ours,
знаю Нет слава Богу у нас наши-то
thank God yours are enough, they
достаточно слава Богу ваших помешала
went on to fight that Great Wars
ушли дальше воевать та Великие войны
push-
отжимания
ups
пережимает
I respect that’s why I say let’s go warriors
Я уважаю поэтому говорю пошли воины
to fight  further, thank God, away from Donetsk
воевать дальше слава Богу от Донец от
away from Donetsk You want to say that
Донецка подальше Ты хочешь сказать что
I
я так
never said anything like that,
понима не произнесла ни разу между
by the way Yes, I agree here it’s mo there is such a thing as
прочим Да согласен тут это мо есть такое
someone’s fantasy t Tom I understand that is, in
кого какая фантазия т Том Поня то есть в
your
твоём
understanding
понимании
the media will
СМИ воевать
continue to fight And what else did you say nothing I’m
дальше И что ты ещё сказала ничего
just saying  that they moved away from
Просто говорю что они отошли от земли
our Donetsk land, went further forward to
нашей Донецкой пошли дальше вперёд
conquer New
покорять Новые
lands, it seems to me that you are
земли что-то ты мне кажется немножко
fooling your head a little Yes, I didn’t fool anything,
морочишь голову Да ничего не морочил
I’m telling it as it is, the soldiers went forward
говорю как есть пошли воины вперёд
further along the Donetsk land to liberate the
дальше по земле Донецкой освобождать
Donetsk land there, but this is what I heard
донецкую землю там не А вот это я слышал
And about the fact that  Well, what did you fantasize
А про том что же что ж ты нафантазировал
in your soul, I don’t know, you’ve already
себе в душе не знаю ты мне тут уже
been assigned to me by a friend. Tell me what she’s
приписала подружка Скажи что она такое
telling us. And the friend didn’t
говорит нам А подружка вообще не
say a word at all, she herself will say, don’t
произнесла ни сло она сама Скажет не
speak for her. I just don’t like it
надо за неё говорить Я просто не люблю
when Kato’s been assigned to me. But come on
когда мне припис Като А вот давай ты
now.  be silent for a little bit And your friend
сейчас помолчать немножко А подружка
will say what she thinks about Akhmat sila Oh,
скажет что она думает про Ахмат сила Ах
I can repeat the same thing that I said
я могу повторить тоже самое что сказала
Mog posh won of course I’m angry heroically
мога пош воны конечно оть злю героически
forward at the cost of the blood of my brothers Oh you
вперёд ценой крови братьев своих О ты
understand
понимаешь
We’re not helping you but we’re defending Russia
Не мы помогаем вам а мы защищаем Россию
Russians for some reason don’t want to fight no
русские почему-то не хотят воевать не
they help how many Akhmats are wounded Yes, we have the
помогают сколько Ахмат раненых Да у нас
Akhmat regiment, we are now Good local
вот полк Ахмат мы сейчас Гуд местно
recovery, when we were I don’t know how it was
восстановления мы когда были не знаю как
with you in Donetsk Yes, but in Kursk we were there are
у вас в Донецке Да но в Курске мы были
no Kursks at all, I’m coming because
нету курских вообще приезжаю потому что
all the Kursks are already fighting on other fronts
все курски уже воюют на других фронтах
No no no no need to Chechnya  they also howl on
Нет нет нет не надо чечень тоже воют на
different fronts, why were there Tatars everywhere?
разных фронтах есть всюду почему татары
Yes, there were Bashkorts, Dagestan was there, and
были Да башкорт были Дагестан был да
Chechnya was there, but there were no Russians. Kursk
Чечня была а русских не было Курской
region, why were conscripts only a little
область почему срочники только немножко
and everything is the same and you have Donetsk, where is
были и всё так и у вас Донецк где это
Donetsk? If you know, it’s interesting that in 10 years,
Донецк Если знаете интересно за 10 лет
our Donetsk men have already passed  This is the case on our
наши Донецкие мужики уже прошли такое и
fronts too, and one thing is that they are not
по ны фронтам и один момент что они не
increasing in
увеличиваются в
number. Donetsk city. There were a million there,
количестве Донецк город Там миллион было
yes, it’s like the whole of Chechnya, like we Chechens
да это как вся Чечня как мы чеченцы
can fight in the Kursk region and the
можем воевать и Курской области и
Belgorod and Donetsk and Zaporozhye regions, and
Белгородской и Донецкой и Запорожской и
probably for this there is a
всё наверное для этого существует
large leadership of the Ministry of Defense
большое руководство Министерства обороны
that distributes  fighters Battalions
которое распределяет бойцов Батальоны
of the brigade by number and by their
бригады по количеству и по их
specialization in different directions
специализации по разным направлениям
can be shorter no in short it won’t
можно короче нет короче здесь не
work here the essence is so
получится суть такая
long it’s hard with you somehow a
длинная тяжело с тобой как-то
girl or maybe sometimes
девочка а может быть иногда
T is the best we are the best Akhmad strength if you
Т лучше всех мы лучше Ахмад сила если ты
look Akhmat is the most equipped the most
посмотреть Ахмат самый экипирован самы
how much Akhmad
сколько Ахмад
to free  lidar liberated Yes, they liberated a lot of
освободить лидар освобождал Да много
Kherson, they took Kherson, they also
освобождал Херсон взяли Да Херсон тоже
took Kherson and the Russians gave it back, tell me, were
взяли а русские отдали назад а скажите а
you at least once
вы хоть раз где-нибудь
present somewhere? Yes, I was in the Kupyansk
присутствовали Да я на купянском
direction, Volchansk direction Yes,
направлении волчанском направлени Да
Kursk Belgorod, we were there, and
курски Белгород мы вот там были
quite recently Yes, well, 3 days ago we were in the
да совсем недавно Да ну 3 дня назад нас
Kursk region  our regiment was returned to Russia for
Курская область вернули в рме на
restoration. How did you
восстановление наш полк Как вы
restore you are
восстанавливали вы
fighting? People are fighting to restore the
воюете ваются люди на восстановление
regiment. There are wounded who need to be replenished;
полка есть раненые нужно пополнить
they look at who else could be, who couldn’t
смотрят а кто может ещё быть кто не
be? Yes, for example, I’m not wounded.
может быть да Вот например я не ранен У
I have a friend, Zaur, he wounded his hand,
меня друг есть Заур он ранил у него рука
but he can  continue in a week He
но он может продолжать через неделю Он
will be in service again and also wounded his arm
снова будет в строю и также ранение руки
in a week in service Well, there is a wound,
через неделю в строю Ну есть ранение
wounded, and there is a wound such that you
ранны е есть ранение такое что ты не
cannot continue to fight. And if he was
можешь дальше воевать А если его
caught a little
зацепило немного
on the
на
bakhmut
бахмуте
bakhh ahma wait bakhmut took Ahmad strength
бахх ахма подожди бахмут брал Ахмад сила
Ahmad took Yes and ahma is  our
Ахмад брал Да и ахма есть ещё наш этот
general Ladina also said yes, that
генерал ладина говорил да что
we Wagner help Ah
мы Вагнер помо Ах
take Wagner helped Akhmat or Akhmat
брать Вагнер помогал ахмату или Ахмат
helped Wagner Wagner helped because
помогал вагнеру Вагнер помогал пото что
Akhmad force is regular units of the
Ахмад сила это регулярные части
Russian Federation and Wagner is a
российской Федерация а Вагнер - это
private military company, he only
частные военная компания он только
helps well who did
помогает хорошо кто взяла
well in the capture of Bakhmut Artyomovsk in  in
хорошо в захвате бахмута артёмовска в
this case, Whose
данном случае Чьи
forces showed more military potential?
силы больше проявили военный потенциал
Akhmat sila Yes, there is. On which flank was
Ахмат сила Да есть На каком фланге был
Akhmat sila? All he came
Ахмат сила был Всё он и заходил
from the solid, to come in, and from the godfathers, yes,
из солида заходить и с кумов заходить да
and how can the solidar come in? If
и может как могут заходить солидар Если
the solidar
солидар ещё
was still a solidar, they took Bakhmut earlier Hey,
был солидар взяли раньше бахмут Эй ты ты
what are you doing?  not from Donetsk means Donetsk is very
что ты не из Донецка значит Донец очень
strange There's just well flan you're not
странно Там просто ну флан ты по не не
not you're not from Donetsk if you if you were
не ты не из Донецка если ты если ты был
from Donetsk know not
из Донец зна не
ahma lidar First take and then take
ахма лидар Сначала взять а потом взять
bakhmut Just bakhmut it was and will be
бахмут Просто бахмут это была и будет
Victory Bach is Wagner that Wagner was
Победа Бах это Вагнер что Вагнер был
Prigogine only recorded tiktok tiktok
Пригожин только tiktok записывал tiktok
and Telegram
и Telegram
etol how many Wagnerians died And how many
этол сколько поги вагнеровцев И сколько
died because Akhmat is strong, he fights
погибло потому что Ахмат сила он воюет
correctly Yes,
правильно Да
he throws like deer, like rams, he runs
он он кидает как олени как бараны бегут
at and oporniki yes, and Akhmat he does it cunningly,
на и опорники да а Ахмат он хитро делает
he looks when it is necessary to enter when
он смотрит когда надо зайти когда оти
he does it correctly  he comes in cunningly
правильно он делает так хитро он заходит
when everything starts We captured And before
когда всё зачином Мы захватили А перед
that the Wagnerites lay down there Well, if
этим вагнеровцы там легли Ну если
the Wagnerites run there like sheep like sheep and
вагнеровцы как бараны бегут туда ЕС и
drive the EU, but that’s their problem Yes, because
гонят но это их проблема Да потому что у
Prigozhin doesn’t have a brain Ahmad Kady Ramzan
Пригожин он нет мозг Ахмад Кады Рамзан
Kady he takes care of our people and
Кады он бережёт наш человек да и соли
wounding the salt yes  And as a result, where is
раня сво да А в результате где сейчас
Ramzan Akhmatovich now and where is your Prigozhin Yes, it
Рамзан Ахматович и где ваш Пригожин Да
doesn’t matter where we are talking about a specific
Неважно где мы говорим за конкретный
historical moment, a specific
исторический момент конкретный
historical moment that yes, look, the flag
исторический момент что да смотри флаг
over the bakhmut raised us Chechen Akhmat
над бахмутом поднял нас чеченца Ахмат
Islam badov raised Soldiers of Wagner where is
Ислам бадов подняли Солдаты Вагнера где
Wagner when the regiment Akhmat Yes first entered there
Вагнера когда сначала зал туда полк
did a cleanup Then  Prigozhin arrived
Ахмат Да провёл зачистку Тогда приехал
wash I was there that you told me where you were
омой я там была что ты расска где ты был
oh it was like a woman they don’t take
ой было как женщина не берут
Nava they blew up some Russian
Нава подорвали какую-то русскую
Wagnerites
вагнеровцы
comment subscribe to my Instagram I don’t
комент подпишись на мий Instagram Я не
know why you are there for what you are there to
знаю для чого це тоб для чого тоб там
marvel at otse mi face Ale for you tse
дивитись на оце ми фейс Але для тебе це
one two yes or three clicks Ale you trime
оди два д або три клика Але ты тримае
me and I will be beautiful Wow in me there Kupa
мене и я буду казати Вау в мене там Купа
fouls and in me there will be a cool mood so that Robiti is
фолов и в мене буде класный настрий чтоб
new cool video letter on my
робити нове крут видео пись на мий
Instagram Popik Andriy Oh
Instagram Попик Андрий О
so let me
так давай я тебя
check for you A
чекаю A